Guide to the William Manchester Papers, 1934 - 2004
William Manchester Papers1934 - 2004
- Series I: Writings, 1943-1995
  - Books
    - The Death of a President
      - Research
        - Interview transcripts, numbered set 1
          - Johns, Lem, p. 853-58 [restricted], 1964 Nov 19 (Box 57)
          - Louisville Courier Journal correspondent, p. 859, 1964 Nov 18 (Box 44, Folder 9)
          - O'Donnell, Kenneth, from the Texas trip folder of, p. 860-61, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 44, Folder 10)
          - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, and Kenneth O'Donnell, p. 862, 1964 Nov 23 (Box 44, Folder 11)
          - Bruno, Gerry, p. 863-67, 1964 Dec 1 (Box 44, Folder 12)
          - Bruno, Gerry, p. 868, 1964 Dec 14, 17 (Box 44, Folder 13)
          - Behn, Gerald, p. 869-871 [restricted], 1964 Dec 18 (Box 57)
          - Wells, Thomas, p. 872-79 [restricted], 1964 Dec 18 (Box 57)
          - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, and Kenneth O'Donnell, p. 880, 1964 Nov 23 (Box 44, Folder 14)
          - Roberts, Emory, p. 881-84 [restricted], 1964 Dec 4 (Box 57)
          - Humphrey, Hubert, p. 885, 1965 Mar 16 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - Interview transcripts, numbered set 2
          - Lincoln, Evelyn, p. A-1-9 [restricted], 1964 Apr 1 (Box 57)
          - Greenfield, James, p. 1, 1964 Apr 1 (Box 44, Folder 16)
          - Gallagher, Mary, p. 2-8 [restricted], 1964 Apr 2 (Box 57)
          - Douglas, William O., p. 9-10, 1964 Apr 2 (Box 44, Folder 17)
          - Douglas, Joan, p. 11-14, 1964 Apr 3 (Box 44, Folder 18)
          - Lincoln, Evelyn, and Mary Gallagher, p. 15-17 [restricted], 1964 Apr 3 (Box 57)
          - Yarborough, Ralph, p. 18-22, 1964 Apr 6 (Box 44, Folder 19)
          - Rusk, Dean, p. 23-25, 1964 Apr 6 (Box 44, Folder 20)
          - Powers, David, p. 26-30b, 1964 Apr 8 (Box 44, Folder 21)
          - Duke, Angier Biddle, p. 31-38, 1964 Apr 8 (Box 44, Folder 22)
          - Holborn, Fred, p. 39-43, 1964 Apr 9 (Box 44, Folder 23)
          - Misc, p. 44, 1964 Apr 9 (Box 44, Folder 24)
          - Bundy, McGeorge, p. 45-46, 1964 Aug 9 (Box 44, Folder 25)
          - Burkley, George, p. 47-51 [restricted], 1964 Apr 10 (Box 57)
          - McCone, John, p. 52-55, 1964 Apr 10 (Box 44, Folder 26)
          - Ball, George, p. 56-59, 1964 Apr 10 (Box 44, Folder 27)
          - Tuckerman, Nancy, p. 60-64 [restricted], 1964 Apr 13 (Box 57)
          - Smith, Merriman, p. 65, 1964 Apr 14 (Box 44, Folder 28)
          - Burkley, George, R.O. Canada, and Robert Weare, p. 66-72, 1964 Apr 14 (Box 44, Folder 29)
          - Kennedy, Edward, p. 73-76 [restricted], 1964 Apr 14 (Box 57)
          - Lincoln, Evelyn, p. 77-78 [restricted], 1964 Apr 15 (Box 57)
          - Dugan, Ralph, p. 79-82, 1964 Apr 15 (Box 44, Folder 30)
          - Thomas, Albert, p. 83-88, 1964 Apr 16 (Box 44, Folder 31)
          - Baker, Russell, p. 89, 1964 Apr 15 (Box 44, Folder 32)
          - Kennedy, Ethel, p. 90-93 [restricted], 1964 Apr 17 (Box 57)
          - Bradlee, Ben, p. 94-97, 1964 Apr 17 (Box 44, Folder 33)
          - Alphand, Nicole, p. 98-102, 1964 Apr 17 (Box 44, Folder 34)
          - Turnure, Pamela, p. 103-07 [restricted], 1964 Apr 17 (Box 57)
          - Clifton, Chester, p. 108-19, 1964 Apr 21 (Box 44, Folder 35)
          - White, Byron, and M.K. McHugh, p. 120-23, 1964 Apr 22 (Box 44, Folder 36)
          - West, J.B., p. 124-28 [restricted], 1964 Apr 23 (Box 57)
          - Burkley, George, p. 129 [restricted], 1964 Apr 23 (Box 57)
          - Gallagher, Mary, p. 130 [restricted], 1964 Apr 23 (Box 57)
          - Hirsch, Jacqueline, p. 131 [restricted], 1964 Apr 23 (Box 57)
          - Hallett, Oliver, p. 132-33, 1964 Apr 23 (Box 44, Folder 37)
          - Hallett, Joan, p. 134, 1964 Apr 23 (Box 44, Folder 38)
          - Kennedy, Joan, p. 135-37 [restricted], 1964 Apr 23 (Box 57)
          - Misc. and Maude Shaw, p. 144 [restricted], 1964 Apr 24 (Box 57)
          - Parates, Providentia, p. 145-47 [restricted], 1964 Apr 24 (Box 57)
          - Walsh, John, p. 148-50, 1964 Apr 27 (Box 44, Folder 39)
          - Stoughton, Cecil, p. 151-57, 1964 Apr 27 (Box 44, Folder 40)
          - Walton, Bill, p. 158-65, 1964 Apr 27 (Box 44, Folder 41)
          - Posen, Walter and Elizabeth, p. 166-71, 1964 Apr 28 (Box 44, Folder 42)
          - Whele, Philip, p. 172-78, 1964 Apr 29 (Box 44, Folder 43)
          - Swindal, James, p. 179-85, 1964 Apr 29 (Box 44, Folder 44)
          - Miller, Paul, and John Metzler, p. 186-94, 1964 Apr 30 (Box 44, Folder 45)
          - General interviews, Fort Meyer: Walter Bishop, Donald Sawtelle, Allen Eldredge, William Malcolm, Thomas Setterberg, Arthur Carlson, Samuel Byrd, and Walter Bishop, p. 196-214, 1964 Apr 30 (Box 44, Folder 46)
          - Shepherd, Tazwell and Mrs. Tazwell, p. 215-21, 1964 May 1 (Box 44, Folder 47)
          - Kilduff, Malcolm, p. 222-233, 1964 May 2 (Box 44, Folder 48)
          - Gallagher, Mary, p. 234 [restricted], 1964 May 2 (Box 57)
          - Guthman, Edwin, and Jo Ann, p. 235-39, 1964 May 3 (Box 44, Folder 49)
          - Bartlett, Charles and Martha, p. 240-242, 1964 May 3 (Box 44, Folder 50)
          - Goodwin, Richard, p. 243-46, 1964 May 4 (Box 44, Folder 51)
          - O'Brien, Lawrence, and Kenneth O'Donnell, p. 247-54, 1964 May 4 (Box 44, Folder 52)
          - Fay, Paul, p. 255-57, 1964 May 5 (Box 44, Folder 53)
          - Taylor, Maxwell, p. 258-61, 1964 May 5 (Box 44, Folder 54)
          - Ormsby-Gore, David, p. 262-68, 1964 May 6 (Box 44, Folder 55)
          - McHugh, Godfrey, p. 269-280, 1964 May 6 (Box 44, Folder 56)
          - Deputy of Charles Walton, p. 281, 1964 May 7 (Box 44, Folder 57)
          - Thomas, George, p. 282-85, 1964 May 7 (Box 44, Folder 58)
          - Bryant, Traphes, p. 286 [restricted], undated (Box 57)
          - Misc. notes based on JBK's files and envelopes marked funeral, p. 287-89, undated (Box 44, Folder 59)
          - Sweig, Martin, p. 290, 1964 May 14 (Box 44, Folder 60)
          - McCormack, John, p. 291-92, 1964 May 14 (Box 44, Folder 61)
          - Boggs, Hale, p. 293-94, 1964 May 14 (Box 44, Folder 62)
          - Baskin, Robert, Misc., (Mary Gallagher), p. 295-99, 1964 May 15 (Box 44, Folder 63)
          - McNally, Jack, p. 300-04, 1964 May 15 (Box 44, Folder 64)
          - Novello, Angela, p. 305 [restricted], 1964 May 15 (Box 57)
          - Nemuth, Ed, p. 306, 1964 May 18 (Box 44, Folder 65)
          - Gawler, Joseph, and Joseph Hagan, p. 307-11, 1964 May 18 (Box 44, Folder 66)
          - Thompson, Llewelyn, p. 312-13, 1964 May 20 (Box 44, Folder 67)
          - Langle, Dr, p. 314, undated (Box 44, Folder 68)
          - Clark, Keith, p. 315-16, 1964 May 20 (Box 44, Folder 69)
          - Hackett, David, p. 317-21, 1964 May 25 (Box 44, Folder 70)
          - Auchincloss, Janet, p. 322-28, additional page [restricted], 1964 May 21 (Box 57)
          - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, p. 329-34, 1964 May 22 (Box 44, Folder 71)
          - Reed, James, p. 335-37, 1964 May 22 (Box 44, Folder 72)
          - Ormsby-Gore, David, handwritten letter to RFK, p. 338, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 44, Folder 73)
          - McNamara, Robert, p. 339-343, 1964 May 25 (Box 44, Folder 74)
          - Baldridge, Letitia, p. 344-45, 1964 May 25 (Box 44, Folder 75)
          - McNally, George, p. 346-50, 1964 May 25 (Box 44, Folder 76)
          - Mansfield, Mike, p. 351-53, 1964 May 27 (Box 44, Folder 77)
          - Harriman, Averell, p. 354-57, 1964 May 27 (Box 44, Folder 78)
          - Luce, Diane, p. 358 [restricted], 1964 May 28 (Box 57)
          - Brinkley, David, p. 359-61, 1964 May 10 (Box 44, Folder 79)
          - Schlesinger, Arthur, journal, p. 362-69, 1963 Nov 22-28 (Box 44, Folder 80)
          - Schlesinger, Arthur, p. 370-74, 1964 May 29 (Box 44, Folder 81)
          - Cater, Douglass, p. 375, 1964 May 29 (Box 44, Folder 82)
          - Gawler, Joseph, p. 376, 1964 Jun 1 (Box 44, Folder 83)
          - Weare, Robert, p. 377, 1964 Jun 1 (Box 44, Folder 84)
          - Morgenthau, Robert, p. 378, 1964 Jun 1 (Box 44, Folder 85)
          - Bradlee, Ben, and Toni, p. 379-82, 1964 Jun 1 (Box 44, Folder 86)
          - Girodano, Joseph, p. 383-87, 1964 Jun 2 (Box 44, Folder 87)
          - Warner, Jack, p. 388, 1964 Jun 2 (Box 44, Folder 88)
          - Bundy, McGeorge, p. 389, 1964 Jun 2 (Box 44, Folder 89)
          - Johnson, Alexis, p. 390-92, 1964 Jun 2 (Box 44, Folder 90)
          - Hoover, J. Edgar, p. 393-96, 1964 Jun 4 (Box 44, Folder 91)
          - O'Brien, Lawrence, and Kenneth O'Donnell, p. 397-400, 1964 Jun 4 (Box 44, Folder 92)
          - Reardon, Timothy, p. 401-04, 1964 Jun 4 (Box 44, Folder 93)
          - Katzenbach, Nicholas, p. 405-07, 1964 Jun 4 (Box 44, Folder 94)
          - Valenti, Jack, p. 408-13, 1964 Jun 5 (Box 44, Folder 95)
          - Gewirtzman, Milton, notes, p. 414, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 44, Folder 96)
          - Gewirtzman, Milton, p. 415-19, 1964 Jun 8 (Box 44, Folder 97)
          - Misc., George McNally, Michael Cook, and WM observations re: drive from Andrews Field to Washington, D.C., p. 420, undated (Box 44, Folder 98)
          - Ayres, Joseph, p. 421-26, 1964 Jun 9 (Box 44, Folder 99)
          - Ross, Barney, p. 427-30, 1964 Jun 9 (Box 44, Folder 100)
          - Carpenter, Elizabeth, Bess Abell, and Mary Gallagher, p. 431-38, 1964 Jun 10 (Box 44, Folder 101)
          - McMurrey, Mrs. Robert Candy, p. 439, 1964 Jun 10 (Box 44, Folder 102)
          - Guthman, Edwin, p. 440, 1964 Jun 10 (Box 44, Folder 103)
          - Fehmer, Marie, p. 441-47, 1964 Jun 11 (Box 44, Folder 104)
          - Radziwill, Stanislaus, p. 458-51 [restricted], 1964 Jun 11 (Box 57)
          - Gawler, Joseph, and United States Naval Observatory, p. 452, 1964 Jun 16 (Box 44, Folder 105)
          - Brooks, Jack and Charlotte, p. 453-55, 1964 Jun 17 (Box 44, Folder 106)
          - NBC report, p. 456-465, 1963 Nov 22-25 (Box 44, Folder 107)
          - Smith, Jean Kennedy, p. 466-471 [restricted], 1964 Jun 16 (Box 57)
          - Addresses, p. 472-73, undated (Box 44, Folder 108)
          - Testimony and depositions [Warren Commission], p. 474-76, undated (Box 44, Folder 109)
          - Mellon, Bunny, p. 477-484, inserts, 1964 Jun 19 (Box 44, Folder 110)
          - West, J.B., p. 485 [restricted], 1964 Jun 23 (Box 57)
          - Reedy, George, p. 486-89, 1964 Jun 23 (Box 44, Folder 111)
          - Macy, John, p. 490-93, 1964 Jun 15 (Box 44, Folder 112)
          - Markham, Dean, p. 494-99, 1964 Jun 24 (Box 44, Folder 113)
          - Goldberg, Arthur, p. 500-03, 1964 Jun 34 (Box 44, Folder 114)
          - Gonzalez, Henry, p. 504-12, 1964 Jun 25 (Box 44, Folder 115)
          - Hannan, Philip, p. 513-516, 1964 Jun 25 (Box 44, Folder 116)
          - Wilson, Frank, p. 517-18, 1964 Jun 25 (Box 45, Folder 1)
          - Wirtz, Willard, p. 519-21, 1964 Jun 26 (Box 45, Folder 2)
          - Fowler, Henry, p. 522-24, 1964 Jun 26 (Box 45, Folder 3)
          - Galbraith, John Kenneth, p. 477-80, 1964 Jul 11 (Box 45, Folder 4)
          - Cushing, Richard Cardinal, p. 481-83, 1964 Jul 13 (Box 45, Folder 5)
          - RFK, Patricia Lawford, Ethel Kennedy, JBK, and Ann Gargan, p. 484-88 [restricted], 1964 Jul 19-21 (Box 57)
          - Dallas, Rita, and Joseph Gargan, p. 489-91 [restricted], 1964 Jul 20 (Box 57)
          - Sorensen, Theodore, p. 492-98, 1964 Jul 20 (Box 45, Folder 6)
          - Carter, Cliff, p. 499-500, 1964 Jul 23 (Box 45, Folder 7)
          - Smith, Steven, p. 501-02 [restricted], 1964 Jul 27 (Box 57)
          - O'Donnell, Kenneth, p. 503. [missing from this set; see numbered set 1], 1964 Aug 6
          - Gallagher, Mary, p. 504 [restricted], 1964 Aug 6 (Box 57)
          - JBK files for November, December 1963, p. 505-09, 1963 Nov-Dec (Box 45, Folder 8)
          - Testimony and documents of the presidential [Warren] commission, p. 510-39, 1964 Jun 27, 29-30, Aug 5 (Box 45, Folder 9)
          - McGrory, Mary, p. 540-44, 1964 Aug 9 (Box 45, Folder 10)
          - Metzler, John, p. 545, 1964 Aug 10 (Box 45, Folder 11)
          - Powers, David, p. 546, 1964 Aug 10 (Box 45, Folder 12)
          - Riedel, Richard, p. 547-48, 1964 Aug 10 (Box 45, Folder 13)
          - Carroll, Bernard, p. 549-50, 1964 Aug 11 (Box 45, Folder 14)
          - Powers, David, memorandum, p. 551-53, 1963 Nov 22-23 (Box 45, Folder 15)
          - Orlando, Mary Ann, p. 554 [restricted], 1964 Aug 12 (Box 57)
          - Shriver, Sargent, p. 555-58 [restricted], 1964 Aug 12 (Box 57)
          - Dillon, C. Douglas, p. 559-65, 1964 Aug 14 (Box 45, Folder 16)
          - Ficklin, Charles, p. 566-68 [restricted], 1964 Aug 14 (Box 57)
          - Office of the Attorney General, p. 569, 1964 Aug 14 (Box 45, Folder 17)
          - Kuhn, John, blessing, and Burrell Peterson, p. 570, 1963 Nov 23, 1964 Aug 17 (Box 45, Folder 18)
          - Freeman, Orville, notes, p. 571-74, 1963 Nov 22-25 (Box 45, Folder 19)
          - The Torch is Passed, p. 575-77 (Box 45, Folder 20)
          - Four Days notes, p. 578, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
          - English, Joseph, p. 579-82, 1964 Aug 18 (Box 45, Folder 22)
          - Thomas, Albert, p. 583, 1964 Aug 19 (Box 45, Folder 23)
          - Hughes, Thomas, to Clark, Ramsey, p. 584-85, 1963 Nov 27 (Box 45, Folder 24)
          - Vogelsinger, Sue, p. 586, 1964 Aug 20 (Box 45, Folder 25)
          - Camp, Christine, p. 587, 1964 Aug 20 (Box 45, Folder 26)
          - Salinger, Pierre, p. 588-91, 1964 Aug 20 (Box 45, Folder 27)
          - Peters, Henry, p. 592, 1964 Aug 21 (Box 45, Folder 28)
          - Carpenter, Frank, p. 593, 1964 Aug 21 (Box 45, Folder 29)
          - Clifton, Chester, p. 594, 1964 Aug 21 (Box 45, Folder 30)
          - West, J.B., p. 595 [restricted], 1964 Aug 25 (Box 57)
          - Shriver, Sargent, p. 596-601 [restricted], 1964 Aug 8 (Box 57)
          - Secretary of Walter Rostow, Oscar Huber, Forrest Sorrels, Marguerite Oswald, and Frank Carpenter letter, p. 602, 1964 Aug 24, 26 (Box 45, Folder 31)
          - Wetzel, Ethel, p. 603, undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
          - Schulz, Robert, p. 604-05, 1964 Aug 27 (Box 45, Folder 33)
          - Eisenhower, Dwight D., p. 606-11, 1964 Aug 27 (Box 45, Folder 34)
          - Thompson, James, p. 612, 1964 Aug 28 (Box 45, Folder 35)
          - Heintz, Marie, p. 613, 1964 Aug 28 (Box 45, Folder 36)
          - Salinger, Pierre, highlights of notes, p. 614, undated (Box 45, Folder 37)
          - Secretary to Dean Rusk, p. 615, 1964 Aug 28 (Box 45, Folder 38)
          - Galbraith, John Kenneth, journal excerpts, p. 616-618, 1963 Nov 26 (Box 45, Folder 39)
          - McGraw, Thomas, p. 619, 1964 Sep 1 (Box 45, Folder 40)
          - Dallas News files, p. 620-624, 1958-63 (Box 45, Folder 41)
          - WM observations, p. 625-27, undated (Box 45, Folder 42)
          - Skelton, Byron, p. 628-33, 1964 Sep 14 (Box 45, Folder 43)
          - Skelton, Ruth, p. 634, 1964 Sep 11 (Box 45, Folder 44)
          - Austin American files, p. 635-36, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 45, Folder 45)
          - Gorham, Dean, p. 637, 1964 Sep 15 (Box 45, Folder 46)
          - Christian, George, p. 638, 1964 Sep 15 (Box 45, Folder 47)
          - Connally, John, p. 639-45, 1964 Sep 16 (Box 45, Folder 48)
          - Rodriguez, Mr., p. 646-50, 1964 Sep 16 (Box 45, Folder 49)
          - Glasgow, Thurman, p. 651-52, 1964 Sep 17 (Box 45, Folder 50)
          - Welch, B, p. 653, 1964 Sep 17 (Box 45, Folder 51)
          - WM observations re: flying into Houston, p. 654, undated (Box 45, Folder 52)
          - Hooper, Wesley, p. 655-58, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 45, Folder 53)
          - Bryant, Jack, p. 659, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 45, Folder 54)
          - Peck, Max, p. 660-61, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 45, Folder 55)
          - Martin, Harry, p. 662, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 45, Folder 56)
          - WM observations re: Fort Worth, p. 663, undated (Box 45, Folder 57)
          - Walker, W, p. 664, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 45, Folder 58)
          - Saccu, Peter, p. 665, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 45, Folder 59)
          - Oswald, Margarite, p. 666-71, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 45, Folder 60)
          - WM observations re: Dallas, p. 672-73, 1964 Sep 19 (Box 45, Folder 61)
          - Huber, Oscar, p. 674-77, 1964 Sep 20 (Box 45, Folder 62)
          - Oneals Yellow Pages advertisement, p. 678, undated (Box 45, Folder 63)
          - Frazier, Wesley, p. 679, 1964 Sep 19 (Box 45, Folder 64)
          - Truly, Roy, p. 680-82, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 65)
          - Lovelady, Billy, p. 683, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 66)
          - Zapruder, Abraham, p. 684-85, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 67)
          - Rogers, Lillian, p. 686, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 68)
          - Landregan, Steve, and Charles Jack Price, p. 687-89, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 69)
          - Rose, Earl, p. 690, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 70)
          - Ward, Theran, p. 691-92, 1964 Sep 25 (Box 45, Folder 71)
          - Examination of Parkland Memorial Hospital with Steve Landregan, p. 693-94, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 72)
          - Cain, Thomas, p. 695, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 73)
          - WM observations re: Texas School Book Depository, p. 696, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 74)
          - Hughes, Sarah, p. 697-98, 1964 Sep 19 (Box 45, Folder 75)
          - Clark of the FBI and Evan Thomas, p. 699, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 76)
          - Connally, Nell, p. 700-03, 1964 Sep 30 (Box 45, Folder 77)
          - Sanders, H. Barefoot, p. 704-12, 1964 Sep 22 (Box 45, Folder 78)
          - Paine, Ruth and Michael, p. 713-17, 1964 Sep 20 (Box 45, Folder 79)
          - WM observations re: Dallas, p. 718, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 45, Folder 80)
          - Whaley, William, p. 719-21, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 81)
          - Sawyer, Herbert, p. 722-24, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 82)
          - Batchelor, Charles, p. 725, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 83)
          - WM observations re: Dallas, p. 726, undated (Box 45, Folder 84)
          - Fischer, Ronald, p. 727-28, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 85)
          - Dallas Times-Herald files, p. 729-30, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 86)
          - Lehrer, Jim, p. 731, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 87)
          - Krueger, Jack, p. 732, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 88)
          - Jacks, Hurchel, p. 733, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 89)
          - Brennan, Howard, p. 734-36, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 90)
          - Anderson, Andy, p. 737, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 91)
          - Dealey, Ted, and Joe Dealey, p. 738-40, 1964 Sep 25 (Box 45, Folder 92)
          - WM observations, p. 741, undated (Box 45, Folder 93)
          - Curry, Jesse, and J.W. Fritz, p. 742-44, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 94)
          - Oneal, Vernon, p. 745-48, 1964 Sep 25 (Box 45, Folder 95)
          - Bullion, J. Waddy, p. 749, 1964 Sep 19 (Box 45, Folder 96)
          - Goldberg, Irving, p. 750, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 97)
          - Sawyer, Herbert, p. 751, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 98)
          - Hosty, James, p. 752, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 99)
          - Lewis, Hal, p. 753, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 100)
          - Dallas News library, p. 754, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 101)
          - Teague, Olin, p. 755, 1964 Sep 26 (Box 45, Folder 102)
          - Thompson, Mrs. J. Lee, p. 756, 1964 Sep 19 (Box 45, Folder 103)
          - Dugger, Robert, p. 757-59, 1964 Sep 22 (Box 45, Folder 104)
          - Lehrer, Jim, p. 760-61, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 45, Folder 105)
          - Hunt, H.L., p. 762, 1964 Sep 25 (Box 45, Folder 106)
          - Walker, Edward, p. 763, 1964 Sep 25 (Box 45, Folder 107)
          - Greene, A.C., p. 764-66, 1964 Sep 25 (Box 45, Folder 108)
          - Misc. notes, p. 767-68, 1964 Sep 26 (Box 45, Folder 109)
          - Andres, Dave, p. 769, 1964 Sep 26 (Box 45, Folder 110)
          - Sanders, H. Barefoot, p. 770-71, 1964 Sep 26 (Box 45, Folder 111)
          - Texas Observer, p. 772-73, 1963 Nov 29 (Box 45, Folder 112)
          - Hughes, Sarah, The president is sworn in, p. 774, undated (Box 45, Folder 113)
          - Poppill, Paul, p. 775, 1964 Oct 5 (Box 45, Folder 114)
          - Buchwald, Art, p. 776, 1964 Oct 5 (Box 45, Folder 115)
          - Carpenter, Elizabeth, p. 777, 1964 Oct 5 (Box 45, Folder 116)
          - McNally, George, p. 778, 1964 Oct 5 (Box 45, Folder 117)
          - Sidey, Hugh, p. 779-81, 1964 Oct 5 (Box 45, Folder 118)
          - Sorrels, Forrest, p. 782-88, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 119)
          - Lehrer, Jim, p. 789, 1964 Oct 8 (Box 45, Folder 120)
          - Cretian, Paul, p. 790, 1964 Oct 8 (Box 45, Folder 121)
          - Deloach, Deek, p. 791, 1964 Oct 8 (Box 45, Folder 122)
          - Harding, Warren, p. 792-93, 1964 Oct 8 (Box 45, Folder 123)
          - Holmes, William, p. 794, 1964 Oct 8 (Box 45, Folder 124)
          - The Zapruder film, p. 745, 1964 Oct 9 (Box 46, Folder 1)
          - Kelley, Thomas, p. 796, 1964 Oct 9 (Box 46, Folder 2)
          - Peterson, Burrell, p. 797, 1964 Oct 9 (Box 46, Folder 3)
          - Lippmann, Walter, p. 798, 1964 Oct 10 (Box 46, Folder 4)
          - Abushch, Helen, p. 799, 1964 Oct 12 (Box 46, Folder 5)
          - Lawson, Winston, from the testimony of, p. 800-01, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
          - Shriver, Eunice, p. 802-05 [restricted], 1964 Oct 19 (Box 57)
          - Shriver, Eunice, p. 806 [restricted], 1964 Nov 2 (Box 57)
          - Powers, David, p. 808, 1964 Oct 21 (Box 46, Folder 7)
          - Warren, Earl, p. 807-10, 1964 Nov 3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
          - Sylvester, Art, p. 811, 1964 Nov 5 (Box 46, Folder 9)
          - Oswald, Robert, p. 812-13, 1964 Nov 5 (Box 46, Folder 10)
          - O'Leary, John, p. 811-13 [restricted], 1964 Nov 10 (Box 57)
          - Yarborough, Ralph, p. 814-19, 1964 Nov 11 (Box 46, Folder 11)
          - Kellerman, Roy, p. 820-27 [restricted], 1964 Nov 17 (Box 57)
          - Peterson, Burrell, p. 828, 1964 Nov 17 (Box 46, Folder 12)
          - Youngblood, Rufus, p. 829-34 [restricted], 1964 Nov 17 (Box 57)
          - Foster, Bob, p. 835-39 [restricted], 1964 Nov 18 (Box 57)
          - Hill, Clinton, p. 840-48 [restricted], 1964 Nov 11 (Box 57)
          - Peterson, Burrell, and Jack Warner, p. 849, 1964 Nov 18 (Box 46, Folder 13)
          - Greer, Bill, p. 850-52 [restricted], 1964 Nov 19 (Box 57)
          - Johns, Lem, p. 853-58 [restricted], 1964 Nov 19 (Box 57)
          - Louisville Courier Journal correspondent, p. 859, 1964 Nov 18 (Box 46, Folder 14)
          - O'Donnell, Kenneth, from the Texas trip folder of, p. 860-61, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 46, Folder 15)
          - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, and Kenneth O'Donnell, p. 862. [missing from this set; see numbered set 1], 1964 Nov 23
          - Bruno, Gerry, p. 863-67, 1964 Dec 1 (Box 46, Folder 16)
          - Bruno, Gerry, p. 863, 1964 Dec 14, 17 (Box 46, Folder 17)
          - Behn, Gerald, p. 864-66 [restricted], 1964 Dec 18 (Box 57)
          - Wells, Thomas, p. 867-74 [restricted], 1964 Dec 18 (Box 57)
          - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, and Kenneth O'Donnell, p. 880. [missing from this set; see numbered set 1], 1964 Nov 23
          - Roberts, Emory, p. 868-71 [restricted], 1964 Dec 4 (Box 57)
          - Humphrey, Hubert, p. 875, 1965 Mar 16 (Box 46, Folder 18)
        - Interview transcripts, p. 807-75, originals
          These files relate to the numbered sets above and the unnumbered files which follow. Page numbers are not consistent with the numbered sets. Restricted materials have been removed.
          - Key to pages 807-75, undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
          - Warren, Earl, p. 807-08, 1964 Nov 3 (Box 46, Folder 20)
          - Sylvester, Art, p. 811, 1964 Nov 5 (Box 46, Folder 21)
          - O'Leary, John, p. 811-13 [restricted], 1964 Nov 10 (Box 57)
          - Oswald, Robert, p. 812-13, 1964 Nov 11 (Box 46, Folder 22)
          - Yarborough, Ralph, p. 814-19, 1964 Nov 11 (Box 46, Folder 23)
          - Kellerman, Roy, p. 820-27 [restricted], 1964 Nov 17 (Box 57)